<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vegetarian Meals Bulk Cooking Patch</name>
	<author>Adda</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.0</li></supportedVersions>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1797189089</url>
	<description>
Simple mod adding three new recipes for cooking vegetarian meals from Vegetarian Meals [1.0] mod by ConZ in bulk – in packs of four – in order to be compatible with Simple Bulk Cooking mod by Lanilor.

––––––––––––
New recipes
Cook four vegetarian fine meals
Cook four vegetarian lavish meals
Cook four vegetarian packaged survival meals

Stats of those meals are the same as in Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ. I simply multiplied the number of food requirements by 4.

For higher demands on those food requirements, I suggest using my other mod called Vegetarian Meals Increased Nutrition which increases the amount of nutrition needed for vegetarian meals so vanilla meals still have a place in the game and vegetarian meals are not that overpowered.

––––––––––––
Compatibility and other mods
Mod is safe to add to your saved games or delete from them. Only make sure to delete all bills with these bulk cooked vegetarian meals from your stoves.

Required mods
Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ – adds three new vegetarian meals copying vanilla meals made just with raw veggies, berries, milk, eggs or insect jelly in any combination.

Simple Bulk Cooking by Lanilor – adds an ability to produce meals in bulk – in packs of four. Does not decrease the amount of work needed to make a meal, only saves the time of your cook by allowing him to cook meals in bulk. Technically, this mod is not required, my mod is a standalone version but was created especially for this mod to run together so I would say it is reasonable to have this one as well.

Recommended mods
Vegetarian Meals Increased Nutrition by Adda – increases the amount of nutrition needed to cook these new vegetarian meals so vanilla meals still have a place in the game and vegetarian meals are not that overpowered.

Compatible mods
Mod should be fully compatible with every other mod. Though if you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning.

Known incompatible mods
None so far. If you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning :)

Load order
Load order should not be affected by any other mods. Just load this anywhere below Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ.

I highly recommend using Simple Bulk Cooking mod by Lanilor and loading my mod right after this one so your bulk cooking recipes are nicely aligned together.

Ideal example:
Core
*** other mods ***
Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ
*** other mods ***
Simple Bulk Cooking by Lanilor
Vegetarian Meals Bulk Cooking Patch
*** other mods ***

If you find any problems, just let me know in the discussion below so I can fix them.

––––––––––––
Credits
Original mod: Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ – I used his meals and just rewrite his code to add an option to cook any of these three new vegetarian meals in bulk.

License
All original code in this mod is licensed under the MIT license. Do what you want, but give me credit.
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
