<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vegetarian Meals Bulk Cooking Patch</name>
	<author>Adda</author>
	<supportedVersions><li>1.0</li></supportedVersions>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1797189089</url>
	<description>
Simple mod adding new recipes for cooking vegetarian meals from Vegetarian Meals [1.0] in bulk – in packs of four (in order to be compatible with Simple Bulk Cooking, Feed The Colonists, Simply Bulk Crafting) or with more options (for compatibility with Master of Cooking or RimCuisine 2).

––––––––––––
New recipes
Stats of those meals are the same as in Vegetarian Meals [1.0]. I simply multiplied the number of food requirements by the number of cooked meals in one go. Work amount was adjusted to correspond to recommended mods.

For higher demands on those food requirements, I suggest using my other mod called Vegetarian Meals Increased Nutrition which increases the amount of nutrition needed for vegetarian meals so vanilla meals still have a place in the game and vegetarian meals are not that overpowered. Comes with full compatibility for every one of listed bulk cooking mods.

––––––––––––
Compatibility and other mods
Mod is safe to add to your saved games or delete from them. Only make sure to delete all bills with these bulk cooked vegetarian meals from your stoves.

Required mods
Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ – adds three new vegetarian meals copying vanilla meals made just with raw veggies, berries, milk, eggs or insect jelly in any combination.

Recommended mods
Technically, my mod is a standalone version but was created especially for these bulk cooking mods in order to add compatibility with Vegetarian Meals [1.0] for cooking vegetarian meals in bulk. None of the following bulk cooking mods is required but mod was designed to work with them together, not to work alone so I would say it is reasonable to pick one of the following bulk cooking mod and for more balanced version (at least as I see it) you can use my other mod to increase nutrition requirements for vegetarian meals as well.

Simple Bulk Cooking by Lanilor – adds an ability to produce meals in bulk – in packs of four. Does not decrease the amount of work needed to make a meal, only saves the time of your cook by allowing him to cook meals in bulk.

Feed The Colonists by PostRobcore – adds an ability to produce meals in bulk – in packs of four. Slightly decreasing amount of work needed to cook a meal. Technically, this mod is not required, my mod is a standalone version but was created especially for this mod to run together so I would say it is reasonable to have this one or some other one of compatible bulk cooking mods as well.

Simply Bulk Crafting by Stein – adds not only bulk cooking options for vanilla meals but also a bunch of new bulk recipes for other common items from Rimworld (drugs, medicine, smelting metal from slag, stone blocks shells and much more).

Master of Cooking by leafzxg and duduluu – adds quite a few new bulk cooking recipes for vanilla meals in packs of 5, 10, 20, 50 and in packs of 10 and 20 for pemmican, wort and kibble. Also adjusts work amount and amount of nutrition required for bulk cooking.

[1.0] RimCuisine 2 Meals and Munchies Expansion from RimCuisine 2 mod collection by Crustypeanut – a vanilla-friendly overhaul of farming that adds more than 40 new crops and a lot of new meals while rebalancing food categories and much more.

Compatible mods
Mod should be fully compatible with every other mod. Though if you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning.

Vegetarian Meals Increased Nutrition by Adda – increases the amount of nutrition needed to cook these new vegetarian meals so vanilla meals still have a place in the game (keeps vanilla recipes attractive for when meat is available) and vegetarian meals are not that overpowered.

Known incompatible mods
None so far. If you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning.

Load order
Just load this anywhere below Vegetarian Meals [1.0].

If you use one of bulk cooking mods listed above, I suggest loading my mod right below one of these so your bulk cooking recipes are nicely aligned together.

Ideal example:
Core
*** other mods ***
Vegetarian Meals [1.0]
*** other mods ***
*** one of the recommended mods ***
Vegetarian Meals Bulk Cooking Patch
*** other mods ***

Load order should not be affected by any other mods but if you find any problems, just let me know in the discussion below so I can fix them.

––––––––––––
Credits
Original mod: Vegetarian Meals [1.0] by ConZ – I used his meals and just rewrite his code to add an option to cook any of these three new vegetarian meals in bulk.

All bulk cooking features mods listed above: I adjusted my mod to have the same features and stats as these mods to include the ability to cook vegetarian meals from Vegetarian Meals [1.0] in bulk as well as vanilla meals.

License
All original code in this mod is licensed under the MIT license[opensource.org]. Do whatever you might want to do with my mod, but would be nice if you would give me credit for the original mod/idea :)
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
